Hello everyone, today we are going to learn how to make such a new style hand-made embroidery pearl dress.
That's also because today is our Qixi Festival, I wish you all a happy Qixi Festival.
Qixi Festival has a strange meaning in ancient times, which is to pray for the best.
Today we will make this hand-made embroidery pearl dress together in Chloe.
This is a detail of our embroidery.
This style will also be used in our new feature of 2026.1, the new method of hand-made embroidery and the four-line function.
Now we open Chloe, click on the canvas window, and import the material for everyone.
This material can be obtained by replying to free material in the official account.
Insert the Qixi style ZPRJ project file.
In this style, we have already made a semi-finished product for everyone in advance.
It uses the function of virtual model 3D pen.
And it has already been displayed as a template in advance.
If you want to know more about this tool, you can go to the financial theme of the National Day issue.
Next, let's deal with this template.
The template is processed into a symmetrical effect.
These two templates in the front.
Right click.
Right click to open edit.
The other two templates, including the back of the template, we just Ctrl D.
Hold down to align.
Then let's check the sewing line.
The two sewing lines in the back.
Let's sew it up.
Simulate it.
Okay.
Next, let's import the skirt.
Click on Connecting.
This skirt is directly used.
We provide a material on Connect.
You can directly search in Connect.
This is the name of the skirt.
Enter the shopping cart.
After submitting the order, you can use it directly in Cloud.
Since I have already purchased it in advance, I will drag it in directly.
Click to add.
Select clothing.
Click to confirm.
Okay.
Then this skirt has been imported.
Let's activate and hide the top shirt.
This skirt will be slightly larger than our model.
Let's put it on the model's waist first.
Then simulate it.
Select all skirt panels.
Reduce its proportion to 95%.
Okay.
Then simulate it.
Let it show an effect of a slightly tight skirt.
This skirt is the base of our dress.
We will add some decorative panels to this skirt.
To present a very rich decorative effect.
Next, let's adjust the skirt length.
First of all, we use the edit curve tool.
Delete the few curve points here.
Then use the edit curve tool.
Press the Shift key to select.
These two panel lines will shift it by 110 mm respectively.
The front and back are the same operation.
The overall skirt length is shortened by 110 mm.
That is, a skirt length of 11 cm.
Then we raise its front and middle point.
Make a curve effect.
Adjust its panel line.
Make it smoother.
The side of the two sides.
Okay.
Let's simulate and pull it.
Now this skirt is tight.
So we have to be careful when we pull it.
Okay.
Next, let's adjust the waist part.
For the waist, we also make it wider.
Okay.
Select these two lines.
Increase 25 mm.
The waist of the back is the same.
When you raise it.
After pressing the left key.
Then right click.
You can enter the distance of movement.
We can look at the translucent surface.
Its current length is basically just right.
Click here to adjust it.
And then we can pull the skirt.
It's so tight.
The skirt is tight.
Anticipate the movement.
And then pull the waist part.
Please look here.
OK, now let's make the waist thin.
This is the waist.
Let's adjust it.
Look at the center of the skirt.
Can you read this?
This is the center of the straight line.
I will simulate it and let it be worn on the outside of the skirt.
Check the left and right to see if the clothes are flat.
Then we select a plate and freeze it.
Next, use the 3D pen clothing tool
to draw a line on the skirt plate.
The curve is probably like this.
Left-click to start.
Press the Ctrl key to draw a curve.
Double-click to finish drawing.
Then we draw the second line.
The same way, left-click to start.
Press the Ctrl key to draw a curve.
Slowly go down.
Then let's draw the third line.
Double-click to finish drawing.
Next, draw the fourth line.
Next, use the 3D pen tool to adjust the curve.
Then press the Ctrl key to start.
Here is the curve we just drew.
Next, draw the third line.
Now we see the curve of the skirt plate.
What should we do with it?
Check it.
The curve of the skirt is more round than the line of the skirt plate.
The gap between several lines
are relatively deep.
It will make the skirt plate more layered.
So that the skirt plate will be more layered.
After the adjustment is almost done, we press the Shift key to select all the lines, and select the internal shape.
After the internal shape is selected, we can select these lines.
We can first lock all the outer outline, then select the frame, and copy these internal lines, and paste them on the back.
Then we slightly adjust its starting point and end point,
to naturally connect it to the back angle.
Then we slightly adjust its starting point and end point, to naturally connect it to the back angle.
We can select these points and right-click to align them to the outline.
When adjusting the internal line with the sound, we can turn it over to check it.
This will be more intuitive.
When adjusting the internal line with the sound, we can turn it over to check it. This will be more intuitive.
Here we can optimize the outline of triangle,
to reduce some of the drawdowns and calls the curves more smooth.
Same thing here, we can use right-click to choosing the optimal drawdown.
Also, we can use left-click to select the optimal drawdown.
After the adjustment is mostly done, will delete all these 3D pencil.
ба
Next, let's make these panels.
There are 4 layers in total, the front is 5 layers, and the back is 4 layers.
Let's do it on the 4th layer first, and then the last layer is directly copied.
Use the round panel tool.
We do it from the bottom up.
Make the largest panel first.
For this diameter, let's enter a 910mm.
Click OK.
This is a zipper panel, we just move it to one side.
Let's make the bottom layer first.
Next, let's use the bottom layer.
Use the round panel tool.
In the middle, left-click.
Enter the diameter of 480mm, click OK.
Then turn it into a hole.
On both sides of the front and back,
Let's make the inner line.
Then cut it off.
Take a semicircle.
On the basis of this panel,
Let's adjust its group.
Select the two lines in the middle.
Move it down.
Move to a front section.
Make it a back-long shape.
Then adjust the width of the back.
Make it a diagonal.
Delete this inner line.
Then pull it out.
About to adjust to this kind of oblique T-shape state.
Then choose to align.
Open.
Adjust its position.
Cool down our skirt panel.
Then we will sew the skirt panel and the skirt panel.
At this time, we need to sew the short side first.
That is, the skirt side.
Then sew the long side.
That is, the skirt panel.
Wait for sewing.
Okay.
After sewing, let's simulate it.
The skirt panel at the bottom is done.
Next, let's copy.
Copy this version.
Copy.
Then paste.
Use the positioning tool to drag it down to the corresponding position and pull it out a little bit.
Then directly sew the skirt and the third layer of the skirt.
We can adjust this skirt a little bit shorter, so that it will be more layered.
Then we continue to copy and paste to make the second layer of the skirt.
Thank you for watching.
Also, first freeze the third layer of the skirt and drag the second layer of the skirt down.
It will not be easy to pass through.
This piece of fabric needs to be sewing M by N free sewing.
Sew the M-line first, press the return key to complete the sewing of M-line,
and then select the n-line, press the return key to complete the sewing of n-line.
Thank you for watching.
and then simulate it.
Arrange the board.
Next, let's make the top layer of the board.
Let's draw a circle again.
The diameter is 580.
The inner circle.
Left click.
The diameter is 295.
Click OK.
Change to a hole.
This is the same operation as before.
Now I drag the circle down.
Also draw the back and front.
Draw the inner line and cut it off.
Adjust the angle.
Make a line.
In this way, when it opens,
when the line is opened,
it will not fight.
There should be a little gap in the middle.
Next, we can sew this board.
OK.
Then we move it up.
Move it to the position near the skirt.
Then freeze.
The next layer of the board is simulated.
The amount of this board will be a little more.
Because what we are using now is a round board.
So the total amount of it will be richer.
You can use hardening to help pull.
Then I also used a fixed needle here.
Then we use it to help pull its board.
Organize its shape.
Okay, after arranging it,
we can unseal and simulate it.
Next, we can adjust its arc.
Then we can adjust its arc.
Use the
drag
to adjust the size of the round pot.
You can also adjust the round pot at the bottom
to make its edge smoother.
Drag to adjust the shape of the round pot.
You can also adjust the length of the round pot.
You can shorten the length of the round pot
to make its edge smoother.
Repeat the process for the other four pieces.
Make the back piece.
Drag the positioning tool
to the back of the model.
Adjust the position.
Freeze the front pieces.
Then we will sew these round pots at the same time.
Use the sewing tool.
Sew the skirt first.
Then sew the white part of the skirt.
Sew the top part of the skirt.
The upper part of the skirt
is also sewed with M-N free sewing.
The upper part of the skirt is also sewed with M-N free sewing.
Pin the M-line and press the return button.
Then sew the N-line and press the return button to complete the stitching.
Finally, we will sew the first panel of the skirt.
Use M-N free sewing.
Remember to change to fold-sew.
I'll simulate it.
I'll pull it to adjust the shape of the skirt.
Avoid penetrating.
Activate the skirt and simulate it again.
I'll sort out the shape of the skirt.
Change the color to dark color for your viewing.
Adjust the height of the second layer skirt.
You can adjust the layers of the skirt according to your own aesthetic and thoughts.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
The skirt is almost done.
Next, let's adjust the top.
Make some details of the top.
Freeze the skirt.
Now, let's make a white decorative line on the top.
It's like a middle-aged clothing.
It's a way of wrapping the edge.
The way of wrapping the edge.
We'll choose the inner border at the edge.
Set an inner border of 5.
Then on the two lines on the sides of the two panels on its side.
It is also the inner border of 5.
After making the inner border.
We choose this panel.
Find the outer of the colon layer.
Then fill it.
Make a colon layer for it.
Then we choose to cut.
After cutting, delete the panel inside.
Fill the sewing line.
Then let's simulate it.
You can see this is a.
Make a relatively floating.
There's three of them.
This is a common way of doing it.
Two panels.
This one is also the same operation.
Choose the outer of the colon layer.
Cut it off.
Then delete the unnecessary part.
No sewing line.
Just sew with a thread
Then we go again
Pull these two plates
Ctrl D
Copy and paste to the other side
Simulate
The back is also the same operation
Choose to add the inner line of the inner line
5mm inner line
Then we go to the outer of the colon layer
Cut
Delete unnecessary plates
Make up the sewing line
This method is made
Wrap the edge and wrap the strip
It will be more floating
It will also be more stable
The back of the other half
After the piece is lined up
We are almost done with this detail
To make it more stable
We can reduce the diameter of the example
A little smaller
I now changed it to 8mm
After the whole is disassembled
Let's simulate again
Now open the random color
Next, let's give the clothes
Replace the needed fabric
The fabric of the upper body and the fabric of the lower body
They are pink body flowers
And this one is made of this piece of fabric
Then in the canvas window
Is for everyone
There is this pink body flower fabric in the material
You can drag it in directly
Use
First of all, all clothing panels
Use this piece of fabric
Then the fabric of its upper body
Still uses fabric 1
Because the fabric of the upper body
It is a pure mesh transparent fabric
Next, let's copy another fabric
Make it the lower body of the skirt
The fabric of the pink body flower
Select all the skirts
Then apply the second fabric
Let's change the color to pink
Click apply and close
Then apply the second fabric
Change the color of the second fabric
Then you can see, it's pink
Next, I'm going to change the color
Like this
Then you can see the color of the skirt
It is 2 to 3 colors
Reduce the opacity of the upper half of the fabric to 2
Because this piece of fabric is in a pure shadow state
Then we can also pinch this piece of fabric
Let it have the function of lifting
Because it needs to be attached to the bottom of the chest
So it needs to be tighter
Then its chest fabric can also pinch it
Let's simulate
Because it needs a more three-dimensional and full shape
Let's pinch the side of the bag
Like this piece of fabric
It has a little hole
Because its piece of fabric is too small
So we can use the setting layer tool
To apply this bag to its layer separately
Click on the left button
To put the top sheet
To put the bottom sheet
It's done once
Layer setting
Then let's simulate
Then these sheets go to the place where it should be placed
Will not be penetrated
Next, let's make this hand embroidery part
There is an embroidery sticker prepared for everyone in the material
Take this sticker out
Drag the sticker to the door of the room
Now let's make a curved sheet
300mm x 300mm
Click OK
Turn off this sticky
Show
To avoid affecting our viewing
Then this
Generally this kind of embroidery flower
It is covered on our clothes
It will cross these sewing lines
So we need to make a single sheet for it
Let it be attached to our clothes
So I'm here
I made a single sheet for it
Now let's freeze the unnecessary sheets
And anti-activate
So we can simulate it more quickly
Now let's drag this sheet
To the model's chest
Now let's drag this sheet to the model's chest
OK, next
Put this embroidery sticker on this plate
Then this plate is used
Use our fabric 1
That is, this semi-transparent sticker
To rotate the embroidery
The flower piece
Good
Let it move
Use our positioning tool
Take a look at it
Which position is suitable for the model
I put it here
is placed on the edge of his chest, and then there is time and space, and then part of it is
embroidered on his chest, and part of it is embroidered on the gauze on his chest.
Now we set the pressure on this plate to negative 10, set a negative pressure, and then
harden it, and after we open the simulation under pressure, it will automatically
be absorbed by the model.
And then I also freeze the top plate in advance, so it's more convenient for us to adjust.
We will change the pressure to a negative 7, the highest pressure, and it will be closely
absorbed by the model.
It is convenient for us to look at its position.
So if we set it to negative 7, and then we set it to negative 2, then the pressure
will change, and we will automatically be absorbed by the model.
So if we set it to negative 7, then we can see that the click is not in the middle, and then the pressure
and shape.
Okay, we will cancel its hardening and then simulate it.
Okay, pull it to adjust to a position and state you want.
Try to let this flower cover its edge line.
In this way, our costume will be more natural.
Adjust the strength to 10.
You can make the board more floating.
Let's rotate the position of this flower.
It's about the same as the model's shape.
Next, let's take a look at the
shape of the flower and draw the inner line.
We don't need to draw a very close edge of the flower.
We just need to draw a general one.
Because we are going to add a bead on it later.
The bead is made of copper wire.
If the copper wire is added very close to the edge,
it will cause the OBJ copper wire to break.
So we just need to roughly draw its outline.
Okay, after the position is completed,
we choose to cut it off and delete the unnecessary boards.
Let's simulate it again.
We can use a fixed needle to assist.
Make a slight adjustment on its position.
Next, we can use a tool to fix its position.
Use the eye-catching tool.
On the flower, left-click,
add eye-catching along its edge at a time.
Add a circle along its edge.
After that, we add a few eye-catching points in the middle.
This will make it more accurate.
Use the move button to select all the eye-catching points.
Right-click, set the layer to 2.
Now our flower is fixed on the outfit.
Change the opacity of the eye-catching point to 0.
Delete the fixed needle.
Let's simulate it again.
As you can see,
the flower is fixed on the outfit
due to the eye-catching point.
Now we can adjust the pressure to negative 1.
Next, let's see how to make a bead.
As I told you earlier,
our bead is made with a thread.
Then there are these small beads in rows.
And its flower thread.
The flower thread is made with a button.
The button is made with a thread.
Then we need to
draw the corresponding inner thread on this flower.
Then we need to draw the corresponding inner thread on this flower.
Now I'm going to impact some thread into thisamine.
Then I press the Ctrl key to sketch its curve.
ones.
Double click to complete.
Then the additional part
So let's first create an inner line with a curve.
Adjust its curve.
Then we select the inner line border on this line.
Re-select the inner line extension.
Enter a 2.5 on its border.
Hook it on both sides.
Extend the number to 4.
Or change it to 3.
Because the width of our beam is only about 3.
After adding the inner line,
let's adjust the details of the inner line.
Select the ends of the inner line.
Then select the inner line.
Then the other is the same.
Adjust it to the inner line.
Next, we drag in all the beam materials for everyone.
There are beam slices,
round beads,
and interval.
There are interval round beads and tube beads.
We will use these few beams next.
First of all, we
Let's make another inner line.
Then use the line section line tool to add these beam slices at a time.
When adding a curved inner line,
let's select the curve.
Then we copy a group of beam layers in the middle.
Then change it to a light color.
Let it have this layer sense of petals.
The petals are darker and lighter.
Then copy another one.
What about the next two sets?
The two sets of beam slices are in a lighter color.
Then use this light yellow color.
Click and close.
Still choose the curve.
In this way, the corner will be smoother.
Then we use the round beads.
We go to copy a round bead.
Use this free line.
Set it to white.
Then hook a circle.
Just like a little pearl.
Also hook and select the curve.
This is a flower pattern.
It is a way of making a flower pattern with beam slices.
Then we will use the same way next.
Hook the edge of the other flower pattern.
These steps are the same.
Just draw the inner line.
Then we use this little round bead.
Add a line operation.
If you want to have other colors.
Or different needles.
You are a bead.
Effect.
You can play your own creativity.
After the hook is completed.
We use the round bead line.
Use the line section line.
Then add once.
Need to hook the edge of the flower pattern.
The inner line.
Good.
After adding.
We need to put these.
The line.
To hook the curve.
Use the editor line tool.
Select this line.
Then hook the curve once.
Let our line.
Its corner becomes more smooth.
After the hook is completed.
We go again.
Choose a flower pattern.
To.
Make.
This.
Lighting.
Effect.
Then.
This flower pattern.
The way of making.
It's the same as the one just now.
Then.
Also.
Go.
Draw.
Many.
Inner lines.
Then.
Because.
Like this flower pattern.
It is.
The border.
Interference.
The inner line.
More.
So.
Sometimes.
We need to.
Go.
To.
Its.
Inner line.
Then.
We.
Choose.
These.
In the intersection.
Add point.
This.
Cut point.
Right click.
Choose.
Divide.
Inner point.
Will.
Become.
An.
Empty.
Point.
Then.
We.
Can.
In.
This.
Line.
Is.
The same.
In.
Interference.
Add point.
Then.
We.
Can.
This.
Line.
Delete.
Other.
This.
Can.
Direct.
Drag.
To.
Adjust.
Good.
Then.
We.
Use.
The same.
Add.
This.
Change.
Color.
Light.
To.
Draw.
A.
Color.
Light.
Next.
Two.
Give.
It.
To.
Choose.
Face.
After.
Choosing.
Then.
Our.
Light.
Basically.
Almost.
This.
Can.
Again.
To.
Adjust.
The.
Width.
Or.
Adjust.
The.
Width.
Of.
Its.
Inner.
Line.
Can.
Choose.
This.
Light.
That.
How.
Adjust.
Width.
In.
Its.
Line.
Thickness.
And.
Length.
Here.
To.
Adjust.
The.
Width.
Then.
It.
Now.
Is.
A.
How.
I.
Can.
Around.
His.
Of.
Half.
Here.
Is.
A.
Visible.
One.
Of.
10%
First.
And.
Time.
You.
Have.
100.
10.
Hundreds of.
We.
Can.
No.
Greater.
The.
jedes.
Men.
Exam.
Since the oatmeal itself is golden, so I also used a golden tube here.
Add it directly using the line segment line.
If you want to adjust the diameter of the tube, you can change it to 0.5 in the parameter variable.
The diameter will be closer.
If you want to make it thinner, you can adjust its length.
If you want to make it rounder, you can adjust its width.
I still adjusted it to 1.5 here.
Then we add the other oatmeal.
Then we add the inner line.
This is the effect of making a small pearl.
Select the opposite direction and change the diameter to 1.
Click to confirm.
Use this round tube.
Use the line segment line to add this line segment.
Click to confirm.
Click to change the diameter to 1.
We can modify its color.
Then select the inner color.
Like this.
Let's draw two inner lines here.
Let's say 2.
Set the diameter to 3 mm.
X-ray the line segment line length and click to confirm.
Click .
Select these two lines.
Right-click.
Click .
Right-click these points.
Select .
Delete excess lines.
Next, let's add corresponding lines.
Use these two lines.
One is light gold.
The other is white.
Next, let's make the flower petals.
For the flower petals,
we use a button
plus
a small pearl.
Add the material to the window.
Use the button.
Left-click to add button.
Then let's adjust the position of the button.
Next, let's use
the
button,
alt-click,
select,
and
delete sẽ
See more.
We can adjust its length and width to make it a little bigger.
This side is adjusted to 2.
Length is 2, width is 2.
And we can also adjust its material to be a metal material.
After adjustment, we will make two more small lines.
Add a line according to the same method.
This will show the effect of shining a pearl.
This is also a process of making a handmade pearl wall to show the effect of shining a pearl.
Next, we will make a pearl leaf with a gradient.
We draw a line in the middle in the same way as the petals.
Then we add the inner line.
Draw a line on both sides.
Add a gradient to 2.
Delete the excess inner lines.
Then we will adjust the position of these inner lines.
Select these inner lines.
Right click.
Add a gradient.
Right click these points.
Divide the inner points.
Delete the excess lines.
Drag this line directly.
Organize it.
Follow the shape of the leaves.
After arranging, select the line you need to add.
Add a bead to the leaf once.
Adjust a gold color similar to the bottom color.
Click to confirm.
You can choose a silk color bead or a metal material.
Let's see which one is bigger
Then let's copy it
Make a gradient color
Let's adjust this color to a light green
Click apply and close
You can also adjust the material
Next, let's copy a new line
Change the color
Change to a darker green
Use it again
Now this gradient is a little wide
So we manually
adjust its diameter
You can also copy this inner line
and paste it on
The inner line on this inner line
will also be pasted on
Ctrl C, Ctrl V
The inner line with the inner line
will be copied and pasted on
Then according to the shape of the leaf
to the shape of the inner line
will be slightly adjusted
Next, let's adjust
The color of the inner line of the petal
Based on its overall color, we will make a final adjustment to it.
Here we make the size of the pearl of the pearl thread smaller.
Then we made another inner thread of the flower thread.
Then we made another inner thread of the pearl of the pearl thread.
Because its original embroidery pattern is also a form of wrapping.
So I added this part of the thread that I just adjusted.
Make the overall layer of flowers more rich.
Open the layer.
Next, let's make the details of the lower half of the skirt.
We used the new stitch method of our paper editor and the tear function.
You can see the effect of this tear function.
Open Claw.
We first untwist the upper body.
After finishing, we will turn it over.
Next, let's adjust the skirt of the lower body.
First, turn on the front piece.
The back piece is also the same operation.
Then simulate.
Now we choose this plate.
We do a furrowing process for it.
We use sewing thread tearing and edge tearing tools.
The sewing thread tearing is may requirerum stripping to have the tear effect.
So, select this plate line and put five mm internal Grübe compassion on it.
After changing the internal line,
We are going to choose this internal line.
We are going to change the internal line and choose an internal line.
Adjust the point in the middle
Combine the overlapping points
Select these two internal lines
Right click, cut seam
Drag the cut out board out
Use the sewing line tearing tool
To select the sewing line that needs to be torn
Left click start, right click end
You can also use the editor sewing line tool
Right click on the sewing line
Select the option to add sewing line tearing
You can add sewing line tearing to a whole piece of sewing line
Select the sewing line
The finished sewing line will show a high amount of green
After all the sewing lines turn green
You can see in the attribute editor
There are these data that we can edit
Next, let's freeze the rest of the board
Then freeze the board that needs to be pulled out
You can see the effect of being pulled out
It's like this
The effect of tearing the edge
Then we freeze the other boards
As the sewing line breaks
You can see that it will form a very natural shape of torn edge
The key to this tearing function is
You don't need your own
To create a shape
Physical simulation will automatically create a torn result
Now we pulled all the edges off
After all pulled off
We can put it on the ground
Right click to save
In this way
We can keep the effect of tearing the edge
Next, use the editor tearing function
Select these sewing lines
After select and activate
All the edge effects will disappear
Select the material
Will use the same material and color as the fabric
Then we can select the main line of the outline
Turn off the end-to-end activation here
Then the main line of its outline will disappear
There is also a long line here
The long line here is the end-to-end
We can turn it off
And the hair-cutting line
We can adjust here
The density and thickness of the hair-cutting line
The density, thickness, length, etc. here
Are the same as our hair
The hair-cutting parameters are close
And its coverage
In general, it is 100%
And its length
The longest can reach 20 mm
And the difference in length and track
These values ​​can be adjusted
You can adjust these parameters according to your needs
And its direction
We can adjust these data
Can make the hair-cutting effect of tearing
Become more natural
After adjusting
Click save
We can save the parameters of this hair-cutting
Save down
You can save to where you know
And give the file
Secret
Click save
After that, we can use this parameter again
No need to adjust it again
Next, we use the same way
On this board above
To add the same hair-cutting effect
We can review the previous operation on this board
Before doing this hair-cutting effect
Let's copy a plate first
On its front
Add another layer
Make a lace-effect plate
To make the overall skirt layer
Can be more rich
I copied the plate here
So we need to fill the sewing line again
Click fold
Here in the fabric
Let's find a lace fabric
Drag it directly to this plate
Simulate
After the simulation is complete
Let's take a look at the final effect
Then we can adjust the length again
Show a little bit below
The edge of the plate
Ok, next we can
Go to the internal line
Use the same way
Right click
Select the internal line diameter 5mm
Expand the number to 1
Click confirm
Check the points here
It's right together
Ok
Next we come to the right click
Select cut seam
Then drag this plate out
Put aside
Then follow the same way
Select these two sewing lines
We can first simulate
Ok, then we can now manually tear it apart
Show this fur edge effect
That because this board
It has more layers
There are some
It turns
It's hidden in a lot of the panels
So we can put some
we can turn on some of the interference plates.
It is convenient for us to pull out these edge plates.
Then we can also hide some of the interference plates.
Okay, after we pull them all out,
we can store the edge plates.
Next, we select all the plates,
display all the plates,
activate all the plates of the skirt.
Next,
we use the editor to tear them apart.
Open the parameters of the skirt we saved before.
The other side is also the same operation.
Click to open the parameters we just saved.
Click to open.
The effect of this skirt is also applied.
Next, let's make this kind of
hollow laser display with this new editor.
This is the effect of the hollow laser.
Okay, we select all the plates.
Activate all the plates.
Then hide the color.
Simulate.
Then we select this
honey-colored flower neck.
Copy a piece of fabric.
Make these two fabrics
apply to the plates that need to become
the needle effect.
Then change its material type
to a wool product.
You can see that now it has become
the effect of this wool product.
The default is a belt needle.
We change the needle method to a flat needle.
Click to open the paper editor.
Our new paper editor,
on the top,
is the preview window.
Set the panel at the bottom.
Click on the arrow icon on the right side of the panel.
You can close the panel.
You can see the preview window more clearly.
Here you can set the number of pieces of paper.
In the simulation here,
you can control the physical properties of the application
when simulating the paper.
Click on the screen on the top.
You can display the paper in front of the simulation.
Open the preview window to edit.
When you click on the preview window,
you can't click on the simulation.
If you want to simulate again,
you can turn off the preview window.
Next, let's take a look at
these new needle methods.
First, let's modify the
horizontal line number and
horizontal line number to 10.
Then change the line thickness to 0.5.
The circle density can be changed a little bigger.
Here it is changed to 11.
Click on the application.
You can try to see
an update change in the 3D window.
Next, let's take a look at
the three new needle methods
of the paper editor.
The three new needle methods
are the circle,
the circle and the corner.
First, let's take a look at the circle.
Select the circle tool.
When we click on a needle,
this needle will hang on the top row,
and form a circle structure.
We can click a few more times
to make this circle structure
become more obvious.
Click on the application.
You can see that
a three-dimensional expansion effect
is presented in the 3D window.
You can see that a three-dimensional expansion effect
Next, let's take a look at the circle.
Adjust the data of the piece.
The line thickness is changed to 1
and the line density is changed to 6.
Let's apply it first.
Click on the circle tool.
The selected needle will
become a yellow highlights display.
Then, click on the selected area again
and press this circle
to move left or right.
By default,
the row can be adjusted to its desired location.
Depending on the desired effect,
we can blooming these lines deal on the selection.
You can set different hole巡 effect
and then it will perform
a brutal or のác ready effect.
and then it will perform a brutal or noac ready effect.
Click on the model
and then we clicking on application.
You can see this hole line
is presented in the costume.
Next, take a look at the сегодня象視塑畫,
After clicking on the flower, there will be a pop-up window like this.
The number of needles on the upper and lower layers can be set separately,
the width of the joint part.
Here you can choose the direction of the twist of the flower, left or right.
Here on the upper and lower layers of needles,
you can set their needles separately,
whether it is a positive needle or a negative needle.
After setting the data for the flower part,
left-click to see the twist of the needle.
After clicking on the simulation,
a flower will appear.
Then we click on the application.
In the 3D window, you can see the twist of the flower.
Next, we use a circle and other needles
to show the effect of our hollow lace.
Here we change the thickness of the thread to 2,
and the density of the loop to 3.
Apply it first,
then use the circle needle method.
Left-click to move a larger loop once,
to create this hollow effect.
On the side of the large loop,
we move a smaller loop.
Switch left and right.
The other side is also the same operation.
You can also make different hollow effects
according to your own design and construction.
On both sides, we can use the reverse needle
to process a diversified needle method.
Then use a few floating threads.
We turn on the simulation again,
click on the application.
You can see a hollow lace needle effect like this.
If you want to make it more even,
we can enlarge this flat data again.
Simulate it, then click on the application again.
Okay, then our style is basically the same.
Let's take a look at the overall state.
On the back side,
we can also use this needle plate.
Select the corresponding two needle plates,
then just click on the application.
In addition,
there are many other updates
and more detailed explanations
for the piece converter and the four functions.
You can pay attention to
the new function explanation
that will be updated later.
There will be more detailed introductions
to these functions.
Finally,
we can change a posture.
This posture
has been put into the free material for everyone.
When you change this posture,
you can see that
this posture is
two arms behind.
When changing the posture,
it may penetrate into the clothes.
So let's do it again.
You can right-click first
and select the reverse-activated virtual model.
After we reverse-activated the arm,
we change this posture again.
Since the model's arm is reverse-activated,
it has no physical calculation,
so it won't penetrate into the clothes.
After the posture is changed,
we will activate this arm again.
If the model's arm is in reverse-activation,
the model's arms will be in reverse-activation.
Let's change the posture.
And then we can switch off the model first.
And then we can shift the position
of the fur to the right and left.
To want to change the posture,
we can press the left button
and hold down the reverse-activated button.
So the model moves to the center.
The top part of the model
moves to the center.
If the model is in reverse-activated,
you can press this button to the center.
to adjust the quality of the outfit.
Simulate.
After the simulation is stable, we turn off the simulation and open Connect.
We can add some settings to the model here.
I used a earring and a shoe here.
You can search for keywords directly and buy them in the mall.
These are all free.
Finally, let's go into the simulation window to check its overall effect.
Simulate first.
The skirt here is a little black.
It's because I didn't open the hair product display.
Then we open it and simulate again.
Let's take a look.
In this way, its display is normal.
We can zoom in to check its effect.
Then its embroidery bead part.
From close, you can see that there are some penetrations here.
It's because our embroidery sticker has a simulation degree.
The simulation degree is 2 mm.
So now we use the edit thread function to frame all the threads.
Change the distance of the Z-axis to 2.
Then we come back to the simulation and check the effect.
You can see that all the threads are floating now.
The button is the same.
We frame all the buttons.
Change the length of the thread to 2.
The button will also be lifted up.
Then we simulate again.
You can see that the button part also appears on our embroidery pattern.
Click on the image to zoom in and check.
You can see that there are some penetrations.
There will be compression deformation.
This is because the inner thread.
It appears to be compressed to the grid.
In this case, we can choose this sticker version.
Then harden it.
Or paste a layer.
Flatten the inner thread that is compressed.
This inner thread is in a flat state.
Then our OBJ thread will show the original state.
There will be no big compression deformation.
Let's do the synchronization simulation again.
As you can see.
Now our inner thread.
All become a very normal effect.
The above is the tutorial of making this new embroidery pearl dress.